(Leonard:)Boy, you sure get your money's
worth out of these games.
(Leonard:)Priya, can I come in?
Sure.
(Leonard:)Oh, God.
(Sheldon:)What?
It's okay.
(Leonard:)You didn't know.
I'll take care of it.
What-what did I do?
(Leonard:)Sheldon doesn't allow flossing
(Leonard:)that close to the mirror.
(Priya:)You're kidding.
(Leonard:)It's a splatter thing.
(Leonard:)There's a little piece of tape
on the floor
(Leonard:)you're supposed to stand behind.
(Priya:)That's madness.
I know.
(Leonard:)Just do it. There's a big
inspection coming up,
(Leonard:)and I don't want to lose
my TV privileges.
(Priya:)You really need
to let me take a look
(Priya:)at that roommate agreement,
one of these days.
(Leonard:)Mm, I don't know.
(Leonard:)I get a lawyer,
he gets a lawyer...
(Leonard:)It's just easier
to stand behind the tape.
(Priya:)Oh, by the way,
a fellow at work
(Priya:)said I could use his
Dodger tickets this weekend.